Hazel Warren papers, 1868-1978 (bulk 1899-1972)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 7: Writings, 1929-1947 (bulk undated), 1.0 linear foot (about 1,000 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  The bulk of this series is unpublished article manuscripts in either handwritten or typescript form. The series also contains the published articles of Hazel Warren. Ms. Warren authored some articles under the name "H.W. Warren" as well as under the pseudonyms "Louise R. Marshall" and "Beatrice Warren." Ms. Warren often recycled paper and would type new articles on the backs of older handwritten articles. (Note: three folders of Ms. Warren's published writings are oversized and are found in Series 9: Oversized).
  - Published. 1929-1947 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
  - Unpublished. (Box 10, Folder 9-21)
  - Unpublished. (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Unpublished. 1931-1932 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Unpublished. 1933-1934 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Unpublished. 1934-1935 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Unpublished. 1935-1939 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Unpublished. 1939 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Series 8: Miscellaneous, 1890-1972, 2.0 linear feet (about 2,000 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  This series includes decals; drawings and paintings; magazine articles; blank postcards; Keith Warren's personal items; items related to the Warren's 1959 European vacation including travel brochures; and Hazel Warren's childhood items including a drawing tablet, report cards, and her graduation essay. (Note: three folders of oversized miscellaneous Native American magazine articles are found in Series 9: Oversized).
  - Buttons; Button-Collecting Articles. 1947 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Buttons; Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Canyon Tours, Inc.; Miscellaneous. 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Decals; Businesses. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Decals; Commemorative. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Decals; Destinations. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Decals; Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Decals; Political. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Decals; War Effort. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Drawings and Paintings; Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Flagstaff All-Indian Pow Wow; Souvenir Program. 1942 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - General; Lace Apron. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - General; Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - General; Miscellaneous. 1908-1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Grant, Archie (A.C.); Ceremony Programs. 1941-1967 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Grey, Zane; Miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Indian Ceremonials; Miscellaneous. 1945-1958 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Invitations; 1941 Presidential Inauguration Ceremony. 1941 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Laguna Beach Festival of the Arts; Souvenir Program. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Laguna Beach Festival of the Arts; Souvenir Program. 1956 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Laguna Beach Festival of the Arts; Brochure. 1962 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Letterhead; Blank. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Magazine Articles; Native American. 1954-1970 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Magazines; Arizona Highways. 1948-1959 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Magazines; Arizona Highways. 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Magazines; Army Exchange Reporter. 1934 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Magazines; Fabulous Las Vegas. 1953 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Magazines; Hobbies-The Magazine for Collectors. 1939-1949 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Magazines; Public Employees News. 1959 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Magazines; West Coast Hobby Manual. 1946-1947 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Menu; Desert Inn (Las Vegas, Nevada). 1955 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Newsletters; Kerley Trading Post News (Tuba City, AZ). 1936 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Pamphlets; Trading Post Literature. (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Pamphlets; United States Indian Service. 1938-1947 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Postage Stamps; Ceylon. (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Post Cards; Blank. (Box 11, Folder 44-45)
  - Restaurant Placemats; Miscellaneous. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Warren, Hazel (Woolsey); Childhood Drawing Tablet. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Warren, Hazel (Woolsey); Graduation Essay. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Warren, Hazel (Woolsey); Report Cards. 1897-1907 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Warren, Keith; Audubon Society Membership Roster. 1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Warren, Keith; Audubon Society Sign. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Warren, Keith; Bibles (Inscribed). 1899 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Warren, Keith; Boys Town Certificate. 1951-1959 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Warren, Keith; Business Cards. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Warren, Keith; Funeral Program. 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Warren, Keith; Military Items (dog tags, signal mirror, date book) 1918-1919 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Warren's European Vacation; Itinerary. 1959 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Warren's European Vacation; Menus for R.M.S. Queen Mary. 1959 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Warren's European Vacation; Miscellaneous. 1959 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Warren's European Vacation; Travel Brochures. 1959 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Woolsey, Lena; School Merits Certificate. 1890 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Series 9 Oversized, 1929-1948, .5 linear foot (about 500 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  - Miscellaneous; Magazine Articles (Native American). (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous; Magazine Articles (Native American). 1930-1939 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous; Magazine Articles (Native American). 1940-1948 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Writings; Published. 1929-1947 (Box 13, Folder 4-6)
  - Scrapbooks; General. 1936-1945 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks; Published Articles. 1937-1948 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks; Stickers. (Box 14, Folder 3)